(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ I KNOW THERE'S PAIN ♪
♪ WHY DO YOU LOCK YOURSELF
UP IN THESE CHAINS ♪
♪ THESE CHAINS ♪
♪ NO ONE CAN CHANGE YOUR
LIFE EXCEPT FOR YOU ♪
♪ DON'T EVER LET ANYONE
STEP ALL OVER YOU ♪
♪ JUST OPEN YOUR
HEART AND YOUR MIND ♪
♪ IS IT REALLY FAIR TO
FEEL THIS WAY INSIDE ♪
♪ WOAH ♪
♪ SOME DAY SOMEBODY'S
GONNA MAKE YOU WANT ♪
♪ TO TURN AROUND
AND SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ UNTIL THEN BABY ARE YOU
GONNA LET 'EM HOLD YOU DOWN ♪
♪ AND MAKE YOU CRY ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW? ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW
THINGS CAN CHANGE ♪
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ IF YOU HOLD ON
FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ CAN YOU HOLD ON
FOR ONE MORE DAY? ♪
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ YOU COULD SUSTAIN ♪
♪ OR ARE YOU COMFORTABLE
WITH THE PAIN ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT NO ONE TO
BLAME FOR YOUR UNHAPPINESS ♪
♪ NO BABY ♪
♪ YOU GOT YOURSELF
INTO YOUR OWN MESS ♪
♪ OOH ♪
♪ LETTIN' YOUR
WORRIES PASS YOU BY ♪
♪ BABY, DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S WORTH YOUR TIME ♪
♪ TO CHANGE YOUR MIND ♪
♪ NO, NO ♪
♪ SOME DAY SOMEBODY'S
GONNA MAKE YOU WANT ♪
♪ TO TURN AROUND
AND SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ UNTIL THEN BABY ♪
♪ ARE YOU GONNA LET 'EM HOLD
YOU DOWN AND MAKE YOU CRY ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW? ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW
THINGS CAN CHANGE ♪
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ IF YOU HOLD ON
FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ CAN YOU HOLD ON
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ OH THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ I KNOW THAT THERE IS PAIN ♪
♪ BUT YOU HOLD ON
FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ AND YA BREAK FREE
FROM THE CHAINS ♪
♪ YEAH I KNOW THAT
THERE IS PAIN ♪
♪ BUT YOU HOLD ON
FOR ONE MORE DAY, ♪
♪ AND YA BREAK FREE ♪
♪ BREAK FROM THE CHAINS ♪
♪ SOME DAY SOMEBODY'S
GONNA MAKE YOU WANT ♪
♪ TO TURN AROUND
AND SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AND SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ UNTIL THEN BABY, ♪
♪ ARE YOU GOING TO LET 'EM HOLD
YOU DOWN AND MAKE YOU CRY ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW ♪
♪ THINGS CAN CHANGE ♪
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ IF YOU HOLD ON FOR
ONE MORE DAY YEAH ♪
♪ IF YOU HOLD ON ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW
THINGS COULD CHANGE ♪
♪ THINGS COULD GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ IF YOU HOLD ON
FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ CAN YOU HOLD ON ♪
♪ MMM CAN YOU HOLD ON BABY ♪